https://www.aquabailers.com/privacy-and-return-policy/

Privacy and Return PolicyHomePrivacy and Return PolicyIt is Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to AquaBailers.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “AquaBailers.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.What personal data we collect and why we collect itWebsite VisitorsLike most website operators, Aqua Bailers, Inc. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Aqua Bailers, Inc. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s websites choose to interact with Aqua Bailers, Inc. in ways that require Aqua Bailers, Inc. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Aqua Bailers, Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for purchases at AquaBailers.com to provide a username and email address.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To External SitesOur products may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.Aggregated StatisticsAqua Bailers, Inc. may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Aqua Bailers, Inc. will not make this information public. However, Aqua Bailers, Inc. does not disclose your personally-identifying information.CookiesTo enrich and perfect your online experience, Aqua Bailers, Inc. uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Aqua Bailers, Inc. uses cookies to help Aqua Bailers, Inc. identify and track visitors, their usage of AquaBailers.com, and their website access preferences. Aqua Bailers, Inc. visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s use of cookies.E-commerceThose who engage in transactions with Aqua Bailers, Inc. – by purchasing Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Aqua Bailers, Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Aqua Bailers, Inc.. Aqua Bailers, Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Aqua Bailers, Inc. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Aqua Bailers, Inc.’s sole discretion. Aqua Bailers, Inc. encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.AnalyticsHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataYou can  request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Return PolicyWe provide a 60 day window for returns as long as the items are unused/unopened. If you wish to return these items, contact us at 1-800-345-6620 or at service@aquabailers.com to be assigned an RMA number.If the product is defective, the entire case must be returned so that we can inspect the quality of both the used and unused products. We will issue a call tag to cover shipping and upon completion of our inspection we will determine whether a refund or replacement is warranted.If the product is not defective, there is a 25% restocking fee applied and shipping will need to be covered by the customer.All custom-made orders, (i.e. non-standard lengths,special requests) are non-returnable/non-refundable unless the product is defective.CategoriesAccessoriesAlconox® Cleaning SuppliesClearanceCordageFiltersGlovesGroundwater Sampling BailersAquaClear PVC BailersBiggie BailersMini BailersPermanent PVC BailersPoly BailersSinkfast BailersTeflon®/FEP BailersPFAS Testing ApprovedRite In The RainVOC/SED Tips
Menu
